byohosting.com 2011-04-26

# Privacy Policy | BYOHOSTING

In short, we respect your privacy and will never rent, sell, or share your private information with anyone. All employees abide by the same privacy policy.

At BYOHosting.com, Inc., your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. That's why, when you visit BYOHosting.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Internet site (www.BYOHosting.com, software & peripherals ) or when you use our online support offerings such as support.BYOHosting.com or our Resolution Assistant Tool. Other BYOHosting.com, Inc. and BYOHosting.com, Inc. Co-branded sites may operate under their own privacy and security policies. For a summary of our corporate-wide privacy guidelines, see BYOHosting.com, Inc.'s public statement.

BYOHosting.com, Inc. only asks for specific types of personal information.

In a few areas on our Web site and online customer support tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate.

For example, we request information from you when you:

Register on BYOHosting.com  
Place an order  
Provide feedback in an online survey  
Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer  
Request e-mail notification of your order status (called "Order Watch")  
Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list  
Request online technical support through our Resolution Assistant Tool  
Request assistance from our "Product Advisor"

In each of the instances above, we may ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, customer preference information, customer number and service tag number, as well as other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. If we ever ask for significantly different information we will inform you. In the case of newsletters or mailing lists, you will be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time.

BYOHosting.com, Inc. only uses your personal information for specific purposes

The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with BYOHosting.com, Inc.. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on BYOHosting.com and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from BYOHosting.com, Inc.. Agents or contractors of BYOHosting.com, Inc. who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for BYOHosting.com, Inc.. BYOHosting.com, Inc. may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.

You can opt-out of receiving further marketing from BYOHosting.com, Inc. at any time.

We will send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only BYOHosting.com, Inc. (or agents working on behalf of BYOHosting.com, Inc. and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of receiving further marketing from BYOHosting.com, Inc. by contacting us.

BYOHosting.com, Inc. will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent

Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of BYOHosting.com, Inc. for the purpose of performing services for BYOHosting.com, Inc.

BYOHosting.com, Inc. will use whatever information provided to us to accurately register domain names. If you would like the information listed with the domain registrar to be different than that of the information you provided you can request BYOHosting.com, Inc. to make the appropriate changes by contacting the technical support department.

BYOHosting.com, Inc. wants to help you keep your personal information accurate

You can request the individual information that BYOHosting.com, Inc. has collected about you via the Internet at http://www.byohosting.com. You can have factual inaccuracies in this information by contacting us.

**Internet Commerce**

The online store at BYOHosting.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. BYOHosting.com, Inc. is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called SSL encryption, (please see BYOHosting.com, Inc.'s Store Security page for details on these security measures). It has always been a BYOHosting.com, Inc. practice to contact customers in the event of a potential problem with your purchase or any normal business communication regarding your purchase.

**Customized Experience**

New technologies are emerging on the Internet that help us deliver customized visitor experiences. At BYOHosting.com, Inc., we primarily use "cookies" to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to your machine and to maintain your shopping experience in our online store. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know any information about you. We might be able to ascertain what type of computer you are using, but beyond that, our use of cookies is designed only to provide you with a better experience when using www.BYOHosting.com. BYOHosting.com, Inc. has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the BYOHosting.com site. For more information about these new technologies on BYOHosting.com visit our Cookies page.

**Third-Party Sites**

Please be aware that other web sites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party web sites linked to BYOHosting.com are not covered by this privacy statement. We use the " " symbol to mark links that go to third-party sites.

You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your personal information, BYOHosting.com, Inc. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**Children's Privacy Policy**

BYOHosting.com, Inc. takes children's privacy seriously. Because we recognize that special considerations exist when kids are online, we have a separate privacy policy just for information about kids (children under 13).

**Rest ofBYOHosting.com, Inc.'s Web site**

BYOHosting.com, Inc. does not seek to collect personal information about kids through other parts of the BYOHosting.com, Inc. Web site. If a kid submits information to us through any part of our Web site and we know that the person submitting the information is a kid, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any purpose, nor do we disclose it to third parties.

**Reviewing and Deleting Information**

Since we do not seek to collect any personal information about kids, and we delete such information that we collect inadvertently as soon as we discover that a kid has submitted it, we typically retain no information about kids that could be reviewed or deleted. In the odd event that a parent requests review or deletion of information about a kid before we have discovered and deleted the information, then we will of course honor that request. 

**Other Web sites**

BYOHosting.com, web sites contain links to other Web sites that are not operated by BYOHosting.com, Inc.. BYOHosting.com, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of the Web sites that it does not operate, and our Kid's Privacy Policy does not apply to those Web sites. For example, the BYOHosting.com, has links to vendors such as Miva Merchant. Please consult their website for their privacy policy.
